{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Wall \u0026 Ceiling Cleaning Services","appliedActionRules":{"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719":"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719_ctrl"},"categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","__cache./api/resource/task/40187/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40187,"taskName":"Walls \u0026 Ceilings - Clean","taskDescription":"Clean Walls and Ceilings","xmTaskDescriptor":"Wall \u0026 Ceiling Cleaning Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":39,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"cleaners maids  painted maid","textMessagingName":"Clean Walls","rolloverLongDesc":"Generally done by housecleaning services, fire damage restoration services \u0026 some carpet cleaning services. For acoustic ceiling tiles, see \"Clean Acoustical Tiles\"","rolloverShortDesc":"Clean interior surfaces.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Clean Walls and Ceilings.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Wall Cleaning \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Ceiling Cleaning","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":13,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Clean Walls \u0026 Ceilings","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Walls \u0026 Ceilings - Clean","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Wall \u0026 Ceiling Cleaning Project","urlName":"Walls-Ceilings-Clean","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Wall \u0026 Ceiling Cleaning Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"clean, maid, painted, walls, ceiling, smoke, remove, wash, odor","emcCategoryOid":-12014,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":495,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40187/":{"taskOID":40187,"originalTaskOID":40187,"setID":495,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":767,"questionDisplayText":"Cleaning Type Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of cleaning is needed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2776,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"General cleaning (potentially recurring)","answerDisplayText":"General cleaning (potentially recurring)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3986,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Move-out","answerDisplayText":"Move-out","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2975,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Heavy cleaning (one-time event)","answerDisplayText":"Heavy cleaning (one-time event)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1534,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Completion of construction project","answerDisplayText":"Completion of construction project","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5214,"questionDisplayText":"Materials to be Cleaned","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What wall and/or ceiling materials need cleaning? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4554,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Painted drywall","answerDisplayText":"Painted drywall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4558,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Painted plaster","answerDisplayText":"Painted plaster","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5977,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Sprayed acoustic (popcorn) ceiling","answerDisplayText":"Sprayed acoustic (popcorn) ceiling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6773,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wallpaper","answerDisplayText":"Wallpaper","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6015,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Stained wood","answerDisplayText":"Stained wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4561,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Painted wood","answerDisplayText":"Painted wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3769,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Masonry/brick/stone","answerDisplayText":"Masonry/brick/stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5215,"questionDisplayText":"Cleaning Needs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Why do they need cleaning? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2783,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"General dirt/grime","answerDisplayText":"General dirt/grime","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6904,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Water stains","answerDisplayText":"Water stains","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1631,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Cooking grease","answerDisplayText":"Cooking grease","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5953,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Splattered food","answerDisplayText":"Splattered food","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5822,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Smoke/Soot","answerDisplayText":"Smoke/Soot","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3903,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Mold/mildew","answerDisplayText":"Mold/mildew","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4663,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Pet stains/odors","answerDisplayText":"Pet stains/odors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2789,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"General odors","answerDisplayText":"General odors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4894,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Prepare for painting","answerDisplayText":"Prepare for painting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":767,"questionDisplayText":"Cleaning Type Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of cleaning is needed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2776,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"General cleaning (potentially recurring)","answerDisplayText":"General cleaning (potentially recurring)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3986,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Move-out","answerDisplayText":"Move-out","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2975,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Heavy cleaning (one-time event)","answerDisplayText":"Heavy cleaning (one-time event)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1534,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Completion of construction project","answerDisplayText":"Completion of construction project","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2776,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"General cleaning (potentially recurring)","answerDisplayText":"General cleaning (potentially recurring)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3986,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Move-out","answerDisplayText":"Move-out","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2975,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Heavy cleaning (one-time event)","answerDisplayText":"Heavy cleaning (one-time event)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1534,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Completion of construction project","answerDisplayText":"Completion of construction project","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5214,"questionDisplayText":"Materials to be Cleaned","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What wall and/or ceiling materials need cleaning? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4554,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Painted drywall","answerDisplayText":"Painted drywall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4558,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Painted plaster","answerDisplayText":"Painted plaster","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5977,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Sprayed acoustic (popcorn) ceiling","answerDisplayText":"Sprayed acoustic (popcorn) ceiling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6773,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wallpaper","answerDisplayText":"Wallpaper","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6015,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Stained wood","answerDisplayText":"Stained wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4561,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Painted wood","answerDisplayText":"Painted wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3769,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Masonry/brick/stone","answerDisplayText":"Masonry/brick/stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4554,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Painted drywall","answerDisplayText":"Painted drywall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4558,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Painted plaster","answerDisplayText":"Painted plaster","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5977,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Sprayed acoustic (popcorn) ceiling","answerDisplayText":"Sprayed acoustic (popcorn) ceiling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6773,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wallpaper","answerDisplayText":"Wallpaper","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6015,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Stained wood","answerDisplayText":"Stained wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4561,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Painted wood","answerDisplayText":"Painted wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3769,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Masonry/brick/stone","answerDisplayText":"Masonry/brick/stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5215,"questionDisplayText":"Cleaning Needs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Why do they need cleaning? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2783,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"General dirt/grime","answerDisplayText":"General dirt/grime","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6904,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Water stains","answerDisplayText":"Water stains","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1631,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Cooking grease","answerDisplayText":"Cooking grease","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5953,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Splattered food","answerDisplayText":"Splattered food","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5822,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Smoke/Soot","answerDisplayText":"Smoke/Soot","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3903,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Mold/mildew","answerDisplayText":"Mold/mildew","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4663,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Pet stains/odors","answerDisplayText":"Pet stains/odors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2789,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"General odors","answerDisplayText":"General odors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4894,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Prepare for painting","answerDisplayText":"Prepare for painting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2783,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"General dirt/grime","answerDisplayText":"General dirt/grime","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6904,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Water stains","answerDisplayText":"Water stains","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1631,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Cooking grease","answerDisplayText":"Cooking grease","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5953,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Splattered food","answerDisplayText":"Splattered food","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5822,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Smoke/Soot","answerDisplayText":"Smoke/Soot","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3903,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Mold/mildew","answerDisplayText":"Mold/mildew","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4663,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Pet stains/odors","answerDisplayText":"Pet stains/odors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2789,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"General odors","answerDisplayText":"General odors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4894,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Prepare for painting","answerDisplayText":"Prepare for painting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}